export const flashcards = [
  {
    question: "What does HTTP stand for in a website address?",
    answer: "HyperText Transfer Protocol",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the name of the first electronic general-purpose computer?",
    answer: "ENIAC",
  },
  {
    question: "What Harvard dropout co-founded Microsoft?",
    answer: "Bill Gates",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name given to an ancient analog computer that was discovered by divers off a Greek island in 1900",
    answer: "Antikythera mechanism",
  },
  {
    question: "One kilobyte is equal to how many bytes?",
    answer: "1024",
  },
  {
    question: "In what year was the Nintendo 64 officially released?",
    answer: "1996",
  },
  {
    question: "1,024 Gigabytes is equal to one what",
    answer: "Terabyte",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is credited with inventing the first mechanical computer?",
    answer: "Charles Babbage",
  },
  {
    question:
      "With over 17 million units produced, what was the highest selling single model of personal computer ever?",
    answer: "The Commodore 64",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What do the letters HTML, a markup language used to create web pages, stand for?",
    answer: "Hypertext Markup Language",
  },
];
